(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-03T04:46:13.678802",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
桐生ココ 3Dお披露目
Kiryu Coco 3D Debut
The cockroach doesn't really have a brain per se,
but it has instincts and a ferocious desire to survive and to reproduce.
Their antennae detect the wind blow,
so the roaches keep their antennae pointed forward.
They're small and can fit their bodies wherever a roach can,
and have a great rhythm of vision.
みなさん！
Everyone!
桐生ココついに３Dになりましたぁ！
Kiryu Coco has finally become 3D!
やったー！
Yay!
みんな今日の放送に来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you everyone for coming to today's broadcast!
見てくださーい！この後ろのヤクザ、
Look at that! The yakuza in the back...
こいつらはちょっと今日緊張しちゃうんで、あの、舎弟連れてきたっす、こいつら。
They're a bit nervous today, so I brought my underlings along.
あの、一緒に踊ってもらいました。あよ、ありがとな、舎弟も一緒に。
Um, I had them dance with me. Hey, thanks to my underlings too,
一緒に後ろ向いちゃうんすけど、
even though we turn around together...
みんなさんがこうして盛り上げてくれたおかげで、
Thanks to everyone hyping me up,
こんなに美しいランウェイに私立つことができました！
I was able to stand on such a gorgeous runway!
わあ！
Whoa!
ありがとみんな！みんなのおかげでございまーす！
Thank you everyone! It's all thanks to you guys!
ま、見て見て見てください！私のこの姿を！
Look, look, look at my appearance!
見て、見て、見て、見て！
Look, look, look, look!
ああ、イケケツ！最高っすね！
Ah, great ass! That's the best!
ちょっと、この尻も見てください、行きますよ！
Hold on, look at this tail too, here we go!
ふうー！この可愛い尻と、ナーフされたこの身体、
Whoo! This cute tail and this nerfed body,
この腰の動きも見てくださいよ！
and look at these hip movements too!
この作詞者に勝てる人おる？おる？
Is there anyone who can beat this lyricist? Is there?
ちょっともう、あの、リハーサルの時点でききれちゃって、
Wait, by the rehearsal stage I was already worn out,
あと、ちょっとね、あの、あのちょっとリハーサルの段階では私、あのパンツ穿いてなかったはずなんですけど、なんでか、なぜか、
and at the rehearsal stage I apparently wasn't wearing panties, but for some reason, why,
あの、雑ボディペイントを実はいま施されまして、パンツ穿いてなっす！誓ってパンツ穿いてなっす！なんすけど、
um, my body was actually given a rough body paint job, so I'm not wearing panties! I swear I'm not wearing panties!
あの、あの、雑ボディペイントされましてね、ちょっとこ、こういう形になってしまって、もう言い訳ないと思ってます！
Um, my body was painted roughly, so it ended up like this, and I have no excuses!
でもね、こんなステージ用意してもらって、このヤクザどもと一緒にアクロバティックにランウェイを歩くことができて、
But still, having such a stage prepared for me, and being able to walk down the runway acrobatically with these yakuza,
超しあわせです！ありがとヤクザ！ありがとボディガード！そして何より
I'm super happy! Thanks, yakuza! Thanks, bodyguards! And above all,
この舞台に立たせてくれた皆さん！
thank you everyone who let me stand on this stage!
感謝の側転をみてください！
Look at my cartwheel of gratitude!
うわあ！ありがとヤクザ！ありがとボディガード！そして何よりこの舞台に立たせてくれた皆さん！
Whoa! Thanks yakuza! Thanks bodyguards! And most of all, everyone who let me stand on this stage!
感謝の側転を見てください！
Look at my cartwheel of gratitude!
うわあ！エイッ！
Whoa! Hyah!
そろそろ体力限界だ！
My stamina is reaching its limit!
本当に皆さん、あの、来てくれて、
Seriously, everyone, um, thank you for coming,
ちょっとね、まあ体力がない引きこもりだからね、まあ引きこもりなんで、まあ、
and well, since I lack stamina and am a hikikomori, well, I'm a hikikomori, so...
ま、快調っすけど、やっぱ快調って現場には出ないんで、
Well, things are going fine, but as a hikikomori I don't go out on site,
快調は現場に出ないっすよ。あの、引きこもりなんでちょっと体力がない、普通よりなさげになっておりますけど、
so my stamina is lower than usual, but
でも、大丈夫です！まだまだ、あ、なにい...！
still, I'm okay! Still—wait, wha...!
おっさんじゃねえよ！でもみんなこの体を見てよ、私のランウェイウォーク見ます、行きますよ！
Don't mess with me! But everyone, look at this body, watch my runway walk, here we go!
これが身長180cmの私の華麗なランウェイウォーク、スレイブイット！
This is my gorgeous runway walk at 180cm tall, slay it!
ありがとうございますみんな！応援してくれたお陰で、見てこのき、
Thank you everyone! Thanks to your support, look at this—
気流界の、大門が後ろに流れてる、
The Kiryu-world's Gate of Greatness flowing in the back,
私のために作られたステージ、とっても嬉しい！
a stage made just for me, I'm so happy!
みんな！トレンド1位！トレンド1位やった！まだまだトレンド世界一、宇宙一になるんだぁ！
Everyone! #1 on trending! #1 on trending, yay! We're gonna become #1 in the world, #1 in the universe!
ドラゴンの世界まで羽ばたかせろ、このトレンドを！
Make this trend soar all the way to the dragon's world!
この尻ね、この尻触れるんですよ。プリンプリンプリンプリン...可愛い！世界一！
You can touch this tail, you know. Pudding pudding pudding... Cute! World's best!
見てこの笑顔、見てこのポイント！ああ、可愛い、私可愛いな、世界一可愛い！
Look at this smile, look at this point! Ah, cute, I'm so cute, the cutest in the world!
それでは、え、ちょっと私が疲れすぎてるから、あ、CM？あ、CM行くすか？あ、ど...
Well then, um, since I'm too tired—ah, a commercial? Ah, we're going to a commercial? Ah, what...
よし、それでは、CMにいってらっしゃい！
Alright, then go enjoy the commercial!
くやしい…
So frustrating...
くやしい！
So frustrating!
どうしたもんか。
What should I do?
どうしたのココっち？
What's wrong, Coco-cchi?
怒ってるみたいだね。
Looks like you're mad.
今日、他の組のモンに舐められてしまったんですよう！
Today, I got looked down on by guys from another gang!
桐生会みたいな極道組織知らないって！悔しいのです！
Saying they don't know a yakuza organization like the Kiryu Group! It's so frustrating!
うわ、それは舐められてるね。
Wow, that is getting looked down on.
まだできて半年も経ってないから仕方ないかもしれないけど、極道は舐められたら終わりだからね。
It hasn't even been half a year since you formed it, so maybe it can't be helped, but once a yakuza gets looked down on, it's over, right?
どうにか組織を大きくするためにも、桐生会を全世界に広めたい！
To somehow grow the organization, I want to spread the Kiryu Group all over the world!
あ、あココっち、もしかしてまだあれ配ってないんじゃないの？
Ah, Coco-cchi, by any chance, haven't you handed out that thing yet?
あれ？桐生会といえば、組織のメンツを背負って、あれを掲げないと、なるほど！と、いうわけで、
Huh? Speaking of the Kiryu Group, carrying the organization's face, if you don't hoist that... I see! So, with that said,
ついに、作ってしまいました！
we finally made it!
桐生会の、金代紋ピン！
The Kiryu Group's Gold Family Crest Pin!
これを身につけて掲げるだけで、組織力アップ！
Just by wearing and hoisting this, your organization's power goes up!
そしてさらに、どこの組のモンかも一目でわかるので、無駄な抗争も無し！
Furthermore, since you can tell at a glance which gang someone's from, no unnecessary turf wars!
カバンにつけてもよし、スーツにつけて出勤してもよし、
Good to attach to a bag, good to attach to a suit for work,
好きなところに掲げて、竜の娘をアピールしよう！
hoist it wherever you like and appeal as the dragon's daughter!
こちらの代紋、なんと、会長のデビュー1周年を記念して、
This crest, amazingly, to commemorate the chairman's 1st anniversary as a VTuber,
配信後に、発売開始します！
goes on sale right after this stream!
本来なら市中に回らない商品ですが、なんと、本日限り、
Normally this isn't merchandise that circulates in the city, but amazingly, just for today,
1500円にて、初発売！
it goes on first sale for 1,500 yen!
みなさん、このライブのブースを今すぐチェックですっ！
Everyone, check the booth of this live right now!
ホロライブ四期生 桐生会四代目会長 桐生ココ
Hololive 4th Generation - Kiryu Clan 4th Chairman: Kiryu Coco
いったいどこまで移動するんだよ、てっか！
Just how far am I moving, seriously?!
なにか、ちょっと時間かかっちゃったみたいで、めっちゃ移動してましたね！
It looks like it took a little time, I moved so much!
というわけで、Welcome to my 事務所！
So, welcome to my office!
こちら、私、桐生会の事務所です！
This here is my, the Kiryu Clan's office!
かっこいいでしょね、見てくださいよ、これ。
Cool, right? Take a look at this.
ちょ、いい感じの事務所なんでね、あの、ちょ、皆さんにぜひ紹介したいんですよ。
Since it's a pretty nice office, I definitely want to introduce it.
これ、ほらかっこいいからね。あの先ほど、スイちゃんも、スイちゃん見ました？みんな。
Look, it's cool, right? Did you all see Suichan too?
桐生会に入ってる人は、ダイモン絶対必要ですよ、ねえ！
Everyone in the Kiryu Clan definitely needs a crest, right?!
あの、必要だと思うんで、これね、あのブースで、ホロライブのブースで販売、二十、二時からされるので、あのぜひ、買ってくださいね！
They'll be selling it at the Hololive booth from 2:00 PM, so please buy it!
あ、そしたら、あの、ちょっと事務所でも紹介したいと思うので、えー、あ、ちょっとあの、射程がなんか、おい、射程こら！
Ah, then, I'd like to introduce it in the office too... range, hey!
おいでよ！おい、射程こら、おい！
Come here! Hey, range, come here, hey!
ちょ、射程きなさいよ、こっちに。もっとこっちこい、もっとこっちきなさいよ、映ってもいいのよ。
Come here, over this way. Come more this way, it's fine if you're on camera.
ちょ、この射程にね、あの、あの、ちょっと撮影をね、この部屋の、いい感じに撮影してもらうと思うんすよ。おい！おい！あ、やろうと思います。お願いします！
Hey, for this range, I want you to film this room nicely. Please!
これね、こう射程の、あの、だ、誰すか、これ、ちょっとツルツルです、私の。
This, for this range, um, who is this, it's kind of smooth...
チンプラスね、まあ、その辺のチンプラスが入ったばかりの桐生会。
A punk, well, a Kiryu Clan member who just got punked up recently.
もう見てくださってるみなさんはね、皆さんよりもただのドチンピラなんで、みなさんはもうね、桐生会の立派な構成員なんですけど、これただのドチンピラなんで気にしないでください！
You guys are respectable members, but this is just a thug, so don't worry!
おい！カメラ用新会！
Hey! Camera crew!
カメラ用新会、この事務所をみんなに紹介すんだよ、ほら！おい！おい！撮影せんかい！
Camera crew, introduce this office to everyone, come on! Film it!
あ、ちょ、私を映してってんじゃいのよ。やっぱ、射程、ちょ、私のボディに興味があるってか？
Ah, wait, you're not supposed to film me. Are you interested in my body?
ま、そんなことはどうでもいいすよ。ま、あのですね、この私の事務所を皆さんに紹介したくてですね、こちら、こちらすよ、ちょ、こ、見てくださいよ、この周りを。
Well, never mind about that. I want to introduce my office, look at this.
これ！ちょ、見えてます、これ？歴代会長っすね、やっぱ私4代目会長なんで、4代目ということで、
Can you see this? These are successive chairmen, I'm the 4th chairman,
ここにね、私が、ま、死んだら乗るすけどね、ま、死なないすけどね、あと5000年ぐらいは、多少は生きようと思いますね。
I'll be put here when I die, though I won't die for another 5,000 years.
あと、こ、このへんを見てって下さいよ、ちょ、このへんを。これ見てって下さい。
Also, take a look around here, hey, around here. Please take a look at this.
どうすか？どうすか？あ、どうすかね？あ、どうすかね？あ、どうすかね？あ、やっぱ、このソファとかね、高級品揃えたんで、
How is it? As you can see, we gathered high-end items like this sofa,
あの、かなりね、いい感じの、座り心地がいいものになってくるんですよね。こっちとかも見てくださいよ、これ、どう？どう？
so it becomes quite nice and comfortable. Look over here too, how is this?
射程こ、こっち、こっち、こっち映すんかい！おい！あー！
Range, over here, film over here! Hey! Ahh!
というわけでね、あの、皆さん、いい感じの事務所をね、あの、ホロライブの、ホロライブの野望をもとに作ってもらいました！やっぱね、しっかり、あの、桐生会なんで、あの、金がかかっているということで、
They made this nice office based on Hololive's ambition! Money was spent on it,
ま、まあ、まあ、まあ、まあ、まあは可愛い私の姿を映しなさいよ。あ、みんなちょっと私の可愛い姿が見たいんすか？
well, film my cute appearance. Do you guys want to see my cute appearance?
え、見たいんですか？どんな姿が見たいんすか？どんな姿が見たいんすか？え？え？え？
Eh, do you want to see it? What kind of appearance do you want to see? Eh?
しっかりしてください！え、会長、会長しっかりしてください！
Get a grip! Chairman, get a grip!
あの、え、ポーズとかありますか？あ、距離近くで、きょ、距離が近いてか、
Um, are there any poses? Ah, close distance, close distance,
こ、タンドルテ！？え、ちょ、この胸動かないんじゃないですか？もう私が自分で動かすしか。
Wait, doesn't this chest move? I can only move it myself.
なんだこれ？ここ固まってよ、この胸。揺れないっすね！もう尻、尻はボディペイントされ、胸はナーフされ、こうね、本当空いてたんですけど、あの、困りますね！
It's stiff here. It doesn't shake! My butt is painted, my chest is nerfed, man!
あ、あ、あ、そういうわけで、あ、ふう！あ、あ、あ、ちょ、みんな、あの撮影会やるらしいっすよ。
So, phew! Hey everyone, apparently they're holding a photo session.
チンピラが、チンピラがね、いろいろとやってくれるらしいんで、あ、ちょっと、見せてみや。
The thugs are going to do various things, so let's show them.
あー、え、会長ニコニコで可愛い私、いろんな表情ができるんですよー！
Chairman is smiling and cute, I can make all kinds of expressions!
ああ！ああ！ああ！ニコニコだけじゃないんだ、私の表情は。
My expressions aren't just smiling.
うーん、ちょっと寂しい感できたり、
Hmm, feeling a bit lonely sometimes,
恥ずかしいよ！
It's so embarrassing!
ふざけんなよ！お前ら！ちょっと乳から取りなさいよ！
Cut it out, you guys! Take it from the boobs!
え？
Huh?
ちょっと、えっと、ポーズしちゃいましょうかな。
Let's, um, strike a pose.
アットホームな職場、あ、もっちろんアットホームな職場ですからね、ここのお便りもいい感じにね。お前も無給でよく働いてくれてるよ。
A cozy workplace—of course it's a cozy workplace, so the letters here are nice too. You're working hard for free, too.
オッケー、いい感じ、いい感じ。
Okay, looking good, looking good.
どうすか？可愛いセクシーショット。
How is it? A cute, sexy shot.
え？
Huh?
え？可愛い？
Eh? Cute?
え？行きますよ、そしたら。
Alright, here we go then.
お、お前らショット撮っとけよ！ほら事務所の大門を後ろにして！
Hey, you guys, take a screenshot! Look, with the office gates behind me!
えい！えい！あー！どう？可愛い？
Ei! Ei! Ahh! How's that? Cute?
皆さんが待っていた爆弾は！
The bomb everyone's been waiting for!
あれの影響で習い切れなくて、できなかったけれども！
Couldn't be done because of that thing's influence, but...
美しい側点を皆さんにお披露目したいと思います！
I want to showcase this beautiful cartwheel to everyone!
行くぜ！ほらショット撮っとけ！行くぞ！
Let's go! Take a screenshot! Here we go!
おら！しゃあ！
Take this! Ha!
可愛いな！
So cute!
まあこれやるとね、体力の消耗が100倍ぐらいになっちゃうんですけどね。
Well, doing that makes you burn like 100 times more stamina though.
それでは、なんかリクエストないの？コメント。
Now then, are there any requests? Comments?
なんかいい、いいリクエスト、ない？可愛い。
Any good requests? Cute ones?
My tail is bitch! どう？私の可愛いしっぽっぽ！
My tail is a bitch! How is it? My cute little tail!
見た？ぷるんぷるんぷるんぷるん！
Did you see? Jiggle, jiggle, jiggle, jiggle!
ちょっとみんな後半にすぎたコメントが、もっと、なんか、こういうの、どうとか。
Everyone's comments in the second half are like, "how about something like this?"
もう疲れちゃってるんですけどね、まあ、会長業務で私いつも忙しいんで。
I'm already exhausted though, well, I'm always busy with chairman duties.
このキリュウココ3D、こちらのハッシュタグを皆さん！こちらのハッシュタグ、しっかり広めてくださいね！
Everyone, please spread this hashtag for Kiryu Coco 3D! Make sure to spread this hashtag!
KiryuCoco3D and for the English users, Join the future JP, this hashtag should be on your Twitter, every time, every second!
KiryuCoco3D and for the English users, JoinTheFutureJP, this hashtag should be on your Twitter every time, every second!
お願いします！
Please!
え、なんのポーズお願いします？腕組んでほしい？
Eh, what pose do you want? You want me to cross my arms?
あ、ちょちょ、いま転びそうになった。
Ah, wait, wait, I almost fell over.
ほら！これが！重鎮よ！この貫禄伝わるか！
Look! This is a heavyweight! Can you feel this majesty?
私の鼻が見たいてか？私の鼻？
You want to see my nose? My nose?
ちょ、横顔を、横顔を撮ってもらいましょうかね。
Let's have you take my profile view.
鼻じゃ！Nose viewよ！
There's my nose! A nose view!
なのポーズしてほしいって？え？どうなん？
What pose do you want me to do? Eh? How is it?
ギャー！ギャギャギャ！だなかのポーズ！ソラノブシのポーズ！どこがじゃ！どこがじゃ！どんどんやってくで！
Gyaa! Gyagyagya! Tanaka's pose! Sora-nobushi's pose! Where is it! Where is it! I'll keep doing more!
え？なんか誰か泣いてる？鼻あったのか？鼻あるよ！鼻あるよ！あるよ、ふざけんなよ！鼻あるよ、ほら！
Eh? Is someone crying? Was there a nose? There is a nose! There is a nose! There is one, stop kidding around! There's a nose, look!
ビューティ！ビューティ過ぎるかい！可愛いですね！
Beauty! Is it too beautiful?! So cute!
この、このチャームポイントのクルクルのかみもね、めっちゃ可愛いですよ！最高だよ！
This charm point with the curly hair too, it's super cute! It's the best!
投げキキス？いきますよ、投げキキス！どう？
Blow a kiss? Here we go, blow a kiss! How's that?
いやあ、そんな色々、色々とな、そんなこと、そんないろんなものをいろんな表情、一気にリクエストされると…！
Man, when you request all kinds of things and various expressions all at once...
ふざけんなよ、目鼻欄のちゃお、こっちはよ、お？手首切りますよ！手首切るよ！
Cut it out, I'll cut my wrists! I'll cut my wrists!
もう知らないよ、塩分も湧きするし！もう知らないよ、もう！手首切りますよ、今！すぐに出も手首切りそうな気分！あーもう無理！あーもう無理リスク回避しよう！あーもう無理リスク回避しよう！
I don't care anymore! I'm gonna cut my wrists right now! Ah, no more! Let's avoid risks! Ah, no more, let's avoid risks!
あの、スタッフがね、力を入れるところを間違えた結果でございます！やったー！
Um, that's the result of the staff putting their effort in the wrong place! Yay!
この美しい事務所で、みんなと盃を交わしたいと思っております！
In this beautiful office, I want to exchange cups of sake with everyone!
お、シャテ、シャテお前、しゃがんどけお前。あのこちらの盃を皆さんとしたいと思いますね。
Hey, squat down, you. I want to share this cup of sake with everyone.
スイスビーかよ！あの、誰からね、誰からね、こんな感じで、こんな感じでみんな、こんな感じで…
Swiss beee?! Um, from who, from who, like this, like this everyone, like this...
みんな！
Everyone!
盃だよ、盃！見てください、この綺麗な盃！
It's a sakazuki cup! Look at this beautiful cup!
このね、美しい盃、作ってもらったんで、
They made this beautiful cup for me,
こちらのね、皆さんの汗と涙の結晶をここにね、お願いします。
so I'd like you to pour the crystal of everyone's sweat and tears right here.
ごくごくごくっ！
Gulp, gulp, gulp!
あの、まあ、まあ、雑、雑だな、これ。ここ雑談よ！
Um, well, this is pretty sloppy, huh? This is a chatting stream!
もう力入れるとこ間違えてんだよ、これ。まったく！
Man, you've got your priorities all wrong here. Good grief!
この盃で本日より皆さんは桐生会！これを観てくれる皆さんは完全に桐生がーい！
With this cup, starting today you're Kiryukai! Everyone watching this is completely Kiryugai!
がーい！がーい！がーい！がーい！
Gai! Gai! Gai! Gai!
こんな踊りができそう。トゥルルルッ、トゥルルルッ、
I feel like I could dance to this. Turururu...
この中、あれだ！
Inside here, oh right!
あ、盃消えた！
Ah, the cup's gone!
ありがとう、みんな！
Thank you, everyone!
本当に、あの、たくさんの人が私と盃を交わしてくれて、
Truly, um, so many people exchanged cups with me,
たくさんの人が桐生会に入ってくれて、本当に嬉しいです！
and so many people joined Kiryukai, I'm genuinely so happy!
おっぱい揺れた！やった！
My boobs bounced! Yay!
おっぱい、おっぱいが揺れないと思っていたみんな！
Everyone who thought my boobs wouldn't bounce!
揺れるぞ！いーい！
They bounce! Yaaay!
ちゃんと映しとけよ、これ、射程、ほら！おい！ちゃんと映して！
Make sure you capture this, range, hey! Hey, make sure you show it!
あの、ちょっと射程、え？ほら、え？射程、から働いてんのか、お前！
Um, range, eh? Look, eh? Range, are you working, you!
働いてんのかって聞いてんだよ。え？うんじゃないよ。しっかりしなさいよ。
I'm asking if you're working. Huh? Don't say 'yeah'. Get your act together.
今日さ、ローアングルをやらないお前は偉いぞ！偉いぞ！
Today, you're not doing low angles, good job! Good job!
よし、許してやろう！
Alright, I'll forgive you!
みんなもね、あ、おっ！
Everyone too, oh!
おっ！これ今、
Oh! This right now,
やーーっ！おい！おい、射程！
Yaaah! Hey! Hey, range!
射程働いてんのか、射程！射程生きてっか！
Is range working, range? Is range alive!
いくで！射程！おら！アウトレイジ桐生バージョン！
Here we go! Range! Take this! Outrage Kiryu Version!
これみんなスクショタイムでは？うわ！うわ！うわ！うわ！
Isn't this screenshot time? Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
ビューティヤクザ！あんたなんて手加減だぜ！
Beauty Yakuza! I'll go easy on a guy like you!
これでな、誰か変なやつが来ても、すぐ虐待、あ、違う、えー、撃退できるんだ！変なやつが来ても全員ぶっ飛ばすたるんじゃい！
With this, even if some weirdo comes, I can immediately abuse... I mean, repel them! Even if a weirdo comes, I'll blow them all away!
着があれば安心！信じられるのは着だけ！ドラゴン銃、USドラゴンアメリカ、ほら！ほら！
With this, you're safe! The only thing you can trust is... Dragon gun, US Dragon America, look! Look!
働かんか！おい！働かんかお前！ちゃんと働いてるか？
Are you working?! Hey! Are you working, you? Are you actually working?
ちゃんと撮影してか、私の美しい姿を！
Are you properly filming my beautiful figure?!
視聴者の皆さん満足してるか？ちょ、視聴者の皆さん満足してます、どうですか？
Are viewers satisfied? Hold on, viewers are satisfied, how is it?
満足してる人手挙げて！あの、満足してなかったらこいつが死ぬだけなので大丈夫っすよ！満足してます？みんなのコメント見せて！
Everyone satisfied, raise your hand! If you're not satisfied, this guy just dies, so it's fine! Are you satisfied? Show me everyone's comments!
え？どうなの？どうなんすか？どうなんすか？おっ！いい感じ！あ、まだ足りない、まだ足りないって言う人もいますよ！
Eh? How is it? How's it going? How is it? Oh! Feels good! Ah, some people are saying it's still not enough!
まだ足りない！おおっ、あ、ちょっと、あ、撮影残念だったな！あ、短い命だったお前は、今何歳だ？
Still not enough! Oh, ah, a bit— ah, too bad for filming! Ah, you had a short life, how old are you now?
うん、30。うん、よかった！あ、まあそれなら十分生きたよな、人間界ならば。バイバイ！バーン！
Yeah, 30. Yeah, that's great! Well, then you lived plenty long enough in the human world. Bye-bye! Bang!
素晴らしい！これが桐流会！みなさんこんなアットホームな職場、いいと思いませんか？素晴らしいよ！
Wonderful! This is Kiryukai! Don't you guys think such a homey workplace is great? It's wonderful!
みんな本当に :-)来てくれてありがとーー！楽しい！3Dでいて楽しい！こんなに動き回れるよ！嬉しい！
Thank you so much for coming today, everyone! Fun! Being in 3D is fun! I can move around this much! I'm so happy!
みんな楽しんでます？楽しんでます？
Are you guys enjoying yourselves? Are you enjoying it?
このね、事務所安全なんで、ゆっくりくつろいでいってくださいね。みて後ろのソファなんかね、
This office is safe, so please relax and make yourselves at home. Look at the sofa in the back,
このへんのソファ、撮影ほら！ローアングルになってんじゃないよ！
The sofa around here, filming, hey! Don't make it a low angle!
このへんね、後ろのソファ楽しんでね、ここに座っていってくださいね。
Around here, enjoy the sofa in the back, please sit here.
まあ私ももう疲れたんで、もう私ももう疲れたんすけどね。ふーー、ふーー、ふーー。
Well, I'm already tired, I'm already tired too. Phew, phew, phew.
お、撮影なんだ？なんだ撮影、ローアングルやってんじゃねえぞ！
Oh, filming what? What filming, don't do low angles!
お、あ、みんなありがとう！ありがとう！お？
Oh, ah, thank you everyone! Thank you! Oh?
安全、あ、そ、みんな安全を疑ってます？コメントの皆さん。
Safe, ah, wait, do you guys suspect safety? Everyone in the chat.
安全を疑ってるんすか？あ、それならこれがあれば大丈夫なんで、
You suspect safety? Ah, if it's that, as long as I have this, it's fine,
皆さん、信頼、安心と信頼のどうすっね、
Everyone, trust, peace of mind and trust—
大丈夫なんだ！大丈夫っすよ、
Don't worry! It'll be fine!
何が起きても、誰が来ても、私が征服…
No matter what happens or who comes, I'll conquer—
っしゃ！しゃっ！しゃあっ！
Hah! Hah! Haah!
やってやるんで、安心してください！
So don't worry, I've got this!
やった！
Yay!
みんなこうお話しして、安心して桐生会に入ってこれるような…
Everyone can chat like this and feel at ease joining the Kiryu-kai...
ぺろぺろぺろぺろ…って、
*Lick, lick, lick, lick*—wait!
すいません、顔に突き刺さった感じがしましたけど、大丈…大丈夫です！私は生きてます！大丈夫！
Sorry, it felt like it stabbed right into my face, but I'm— I'm fine! I'm alive! I'm fine!
あの、はぁはぁ…
Um, *huff, huff*...
めちゃめちゃ動き回ると疲れるんですね、やっぱり。あの、疲れちゃうよ。あの、お、お、お！さて！
Moving around a lot is pretty tiring, huh? It wears you out. Um, hey! Now then!
お前！お前もうちょっとこっち来て。
Hey you! Come a little closer over here.
あの、私は動きたくないから、もうお前が動き回れ。私を撮影するのだ。
Um, I don't want to move, so you're gonna run around. Your job is to film me!
あー、美しい！可愛い！
Ah, gorgeous! So cute!
この後ろ姿を撮ってるのか？桐生の背中よ！
Are you filming my back? Behold Kiryu's back!
ほらほらほら…これ、私の
Look, look, look... This is my
ドラゴンテイル！竜のしっぽ可愛いでしょう？可愛いじゃん、可愛いじゃん！
Dragon Tail! Isn't a dragon tail cute? It's so cute!
あの、これね、こんなにたくさん揺れて、自然に、こんなにみんなを…バーン！
Um, you see, it shakes so much, naturally shaking everyone like... Bam!
しっぽアタック！しっぽアタック！できるんで、いつでもしてほしい人は言ってくださいね。
Tail attack! Tail attack! I can do that, so if anyone ever wants me to do it, just let me know.
いつでも言ってくださいよね！やーい！
Be sure to tell me anytime! Yay!
あの、はぁ、はぁ、はぁ…
Um, *huff, huff, huff*...
ドラゴンテイル！あ…
Dragon Tail! Ah...
People from overseas, thank you so much for coming! This is your Dragon Waifu! Yay!
In 3D for the first time! Yes, legendary! ガン！
In 3D for the first time! Yes, legendary! Gun!
エイ、ロック、ア、マイ、ボディ！あ、カモン！シェイクン！
Rock, a, my, body! Ah, come on! Shaken!
イエス！
Yes!
そしたら、あ、もういいよお前。ちょっと帰れ、帰れ。あ、帰れじゃない全く。
Then, ah, forget it, you. Just go away, go away. Ah, not "go away," geez.
みんな…このね、事務所をね、こうやってぐりぐりかい…くれて、ありがとうございます！素敵な事務所、これからも大切に私の活動で使っていきたいと、思います！イェーイ！
Everyone... thank you so much for looking all around and showing us this office! I want to keep cherishing this wonderful office for my activities! Yay!
こんな、こんな綺麗な事務所だからな、なんか、もったいないの。ね、もったいない。
Since it's such a gorgeous office, somehow, it feels like a waste. Right, what a waste.
あの、ここの事務所にはね、あの、4期生のね、角巻とかも今後招待する予定なんすよ。やっぱ、ね？
Um, as for this office, you know, I plan to invite 4th gen members like Tsunomaki and others here in the future too. I mean, right?
やっぱどうせなら一番最初は角巻ですとか、綿芽ですとか、わためぇとか、トワとか、やっぱ同期をね、呼びたいすね、まだ。あと、ちょっと、あの、もっと掃除しないと先輩は呼べない。
If we're gonna do it, the very first should be Tsunomaki, or Watame, or Watame, or Towa... I wanna call my genmates first. Also, I need to clean up a bit more before I can invite my senpais.
あの、先輩たちを呼ぶにはまだ早いかもしれないですから、
It might still be a bit too early to invite our senpais, so
ちょっとこの辺とか綺麗に掃除して、掃除してね。あの、この辺とかも綺麗に掃除してね、掃除してね。あの、やらないといけないとは思うのですが、
I need to clean this area up nicely. Clean it up, you know. Clean this area up nicely too, clean it up! I feel like I have to do that,
でも、あの、もうちょっと、あの、綺麗になったらね、みんなを呼んでここで、あの、ホロライブだいだんぎとかしたん、あの、なんていうの？ホロライブだんご？な、なんていうんでしたっけ？3つ入国？なんていうんでしたっけ？そういうのやっていきたいと思いますので、
but once it gets a bit cleaner, I want to call everyone here and do a Hololive big discussion—um, what's it called? Hololive dumpling? W-what was it called again? Three-item entry? What was it called? I want to do stuff like that,
皆さん、あの、どうかどうか楽しみにしていてくださいね！イェーイ！
so everyone, please look forward to it! Yay!
はぁ、疲れちゃった。ちょっと後ろの椅子に座って休もうかな、休みましょうかな。疲れちゃったな。
*Sigh*, I'm tired. Should I sit on the chair in the back and rest? Let's take a break. I'm so tired.
でもまだまだ、まだまだ配信は続くんだじゃん！みんな最後まで見ていってくださいね！
But the stream is still gonna keep going! Everyone, make sure to watch all the way to the end!
あ、もうちょっとポーズする時間がある。あ、ちょっと、ちょっとね、あのポーズしちゃおうかな。みんなの求めているポーズは、
Ah, I have a bit more time for poses. Ah, let's strike a pose. The pose everyone is looking for...
でもみんなの求めているのこれ でしょ？私の、こう膝にルーナたんを乗せるのが、ルーナたんを乗せるのが、あ！楽しみだ！
I mean, everyone wants this one, right? Me putting Luna-tan on my knees, putting Luna-tan on my knees—Ah! I'm looking forward to it!
あの、私のね、あの、皆さんの身長に合わせようとすると、どうしてもねこうなってしまうので、あの、こちらのポーズは絶対に必要かと思う。
Whenever I try to match everyone's height, it always ends up like this, so I think this pose is definitely necessary.
あとは、あの、よくね、みんなの身長に合わせるために私いろんなポーズしてるんですけど、ま、こうやってね、みんなと合わせたり、180cmなんでどうして もね…オケー！
Also, I do various poses to match everyone's height, like matching with you all. Since I'm 180cm, it's bound to... Okay!
あとどんなポーズ？そのポーズ好き？え？ルーナ、ルーナちゃんトイディはよ？本当ですよ。3Dになったら、みんなをこの膝に乗せるんだ！やった！完璧！
What other pose? You like that pose? Eh? Luna-chan, Toyde fast? Seriously. Once it's in 3D, I'm gonna put everyone on these knees! Yay! Perfect!
どんなポーズ？伝説のポーズ？伝説のポーズってなんですか？ま、みんなの身長に合わせるには私が犠牲になるしかなかったのだ。
What pose? Legendary pose? What's a legendary pose? Well, to match everyone's height, I had no choice but to be the sacrifice.
これあのね、あの、中指を立てるな…えっ？えっ？えっ？
This, you know... wait, don't flip the middle finger... Eh? Eh? Eh?
なんか突然、突然椅子…
Suddenly, suddenly the chair...
椅子スライドしてしてきたんですけど、
I slid the chair over,
ちょっとすいません。
Excuse me for a second.
椅子どこじゃない。椅子どこじゃない。
Not the chair! Not the chair!
なんだよこの椅子。
What is this chair?!
ちょっ、あの、椅子行っちゃったよ。
Wait, um, the chair went away!
なに今の? 座らせてくれるんじゃないんかい、ふざけんじゃねえよ。
What was that? Aren't you going to let me sit? Don't mess with me!
え、え、え、え、ちょっ、待て、待て、待て、待て、ふざけんじゃねえ、ふざけんじゃねえ！
W-Wait, wait, wait, wait, don't mess with me—
あら！痛い！
Ouch! That hurts!
あ、そうか。ちょっ、ふざけんな。ふざけんじゃねえよ。あ、ふざけんじゃねえよ。
Ah, I see. Hey, don't mess with me. Don't mess with me.
なんてめ、なんだお前、なんだてめ、なんだてめ、ふざけんじゃねえよ。ふざけんじゃねえ！
What do you think you're doing? What are you, what the hell, don't mess with me!
ふざけんな！ふざけんじゃねえよ！
Don't mess with me!
いてっ！
Ouch!
勝ち込め！勝ち込め！
Win! Win!
動くじゃないぞ。
Don't move.
ここ、あかんじゃない。ちょっと移動しますわ。
This isn't allowed. Let's move a bit.
ごめん、ちょっと最後にほら。
Sorry, lastly, look.
ほら、オッケーオッケーオッケーオッケー。
Look, okay, okay, okay, okay.
おわー！
Whoa!
くやしー くやしー どうしたもんか
So frustrating... so frustrating... What should I do?
どうしたのここち 送ってるみたいだね
What's wrong, Kokochi? It sounds like you're depressed.
今日 他の組の門に 舐められてしまったんですよう
Today, we were looked down upon by another family's gates!
流血みたいな ヤクソウソウシキ 知らないって！ くやしいのです！
A bloodshed-like herbal medicine funeral? I don't know that! It's so frustrating!
うわ それは舐められてるね
Whoa, that's being looked down on.
まだできて半年も経ってないから仕方ないかもしれないけど 僕らは舐められたら終わりだからね
It hasn't even been half a year since we were formed, so maybe it can't be helped, but for us, once we're looked down on, it's over.
とにかく 組織を大きくするためにも 流血会を 全世界に広めたい！
Anyway, to make the organization bigger, I want to spread the Ryuketsukai to the entire world!
ううー！
Ooh!
あ！あ、ここち もしかしてまだあれ配ってないんじゃないの？
Ah! Ah, Kokochi, could it be you haven't distributed *that* yet?
あれ？ 極道といえば 組織の滅を背負って あれを掲げないと！
Huh? Speaking of the Yakuza, carrying the fate of the organization, you have to hold *that* up!
なるほど！ と言うわけで ついに 作ってしまいました！
I see! And so, we finally made it!
流血会の 金代紋ピン！ これを身につけて 掲げるだけで
The Ryuketsukai's Gold Crest Pin! Just wearing this and holding it up,
組織力アップ！
organization power up!
そして さらに どこ の組の門かも 一目でわかるので 無駄な抗争も なし！
And furthermore, since you can tell which family's gate at a glance, pointless conflicts are none!
カバンにつけてもよし スーツにつけて出勤してもよし 好きなところに掲げて 竜の仔をアピールしよう！
Good on a bag, good on a suit for commuting! Hang it wherever you like and appeal as a Dragon Cub!
こちらのダイモ なんと 会長の3D化を記念して
And this crest, amazingly, to commemorate the Chairman's 3Dization,
配信後に 発売開始！ やったー！
starting sales right after the stream! Yay!
本来なら 市庁に出回らない商品ですが なんと 本日限り！
Normally, this isn't an item distributed in the city hall, but amazingly, for today only!
1500円にて 発売！
released at 1,500 yen!
みなさん、 このライブのブースを 今すぐ チェックですよ！
Everyone, check out the live's BOOTH right now!
イヤー！ こちら朝ココのねCM撮影でたくさん使ったお部屋になります。こちらの部屋も今日3Dになってお披露目なんだ！
YAY! This room was used a lot in AsaCoco's CM shooting. This room also became 3D today and is being unveiled!
みなさん、今日はですね、こう大モンのCMに...
Everyone, today, for the CM of the Dai-mon...
買い物流してんじゃねえよ全く、
Stop streaming my purchases, seriously,
2回も流してんじゃねえよ！
stop streaming it twice!
あの、あちらの台も、あの、22、22ミリになってるんですけども、22ミリになってるんですけども、
That table over there is also... well, it's 22, 22 millimeters, it's become 22 millimeters,
私一回り大きいの持ってんで、私トップなんでね。
but I have one a size bigger, since I'm at the top.
トップなほど、私はトップなのだね。
Being at the top, I'm at the top, you see.
あの、一回り大きいの持ってマス。だから私が一回り大きいのつけて
I have one a size bigger. So, I put on a size bigger
子分の君たちは、皆さんは小さいのをつけて
and you subordinates, everyone puts on the smaller ones,
みんなで桐生会を盛り上げていってほしいと、思います！
and I want everyone to hype up the Kiryukai together!
みんな本当のありがとうございます。
Thank you all so much.
ていうかさっきもヤクザ、何だったのさっきの。
Wait, what was that yakuza thing just now?
事務所に、事務所になんかやばいヤクザ来てましたけど。
Some dangerous yakuza came to the office.
あ、かち込まれたんすよね、ちょもう
Ah, it got ambushed, right? Seriously...
いや、もうなんかバレちゃったんすかね私の事務所の場所。
Man, I wonder if the location of my office got exposed.
ここなら安全ですけどね。
It's safe here, though.
え、でもバレちゃったんすかね？え、もうあそこ安全じゃないよ、もう。
Wait, do you think it got leaked? It's not safe there anymore!
え、どうしよう、もうあそこ安全じゃないよ。
What should I do, it's not safe there anymore.
え、みんなどうします？
What do you guys do?
あんな、せっかく作ってもらったとこもう、かち込まれて使えなくなってしまった。
Man, the place they specially made for me got attacked and can't be used anymore.
悲しい、悲しい。
So sad, so sad.
でも、やっぱりもう、もうあんな危ないところにいるってことはもうできないですから。
But, you know, being in such a dangerous place anymore is impossible now.
でももうヤクザに目つけられちゃったってことはもうやっぱ私アイドルになるしかないのかもしれない。
But since I got noticed by the yakuza, maybe I really have no choice but to become an idol.
やっぱりホロライブといえばアイドル！
After all, when you think of Hololive, it's idols!
私はヤクザではなく、アイドルを目指すべきだったのでしょうか！
I am not a yakuza, but should I have aimed to be an idol instead?!
あぶないもんね、命がけだもんね。
It's dangerous, after all. It's life-threatening.
ヤクザはよ、みんなよ、あ！朝ココ商品が、
Hey yakuza, everyone, ah! Asacoco products...
朝ココ商品がこんなにもたくさん、みんなありがとう、朝ココ商品を買ってくれてありがとう、
So many Asacoco products, thank you everyone, thank you for buying Asacoco products,
スーパーチャットいただいたみなさんの、みなさんの、商品がこちらに、
and to everyone who gave super chats, your products are right here—
あの今スーパークラッチいただきますとね、このようね、あの朝ココ商品が皆さんの脳に直接届きますので、脳直です！
if you give a super chat right now, like this, Asacoco products go directly to your brains, brain direct!
脳直です！今皆さんのところに朝ココ商品が届いてんで！ほら！私あそこだ、私あそこだ！
Direct to your brain! Asacoco products are reaching you right now! Look! That's me, that's me!
私をうつさんかい！ほら！私をうつさんかい！あ、みなさんありがとうございます、
Point the camera at me! Come on! Point the camera at me! Ah, thank you everyone,
たくさんスーパーチャットいただいたって、ありがとうございます、嬉しい！
for getting so many super chats, thank you, I'm so happy!
みなさん本当にありがとうございます！ていうか、
Thank you everyone, truly! Also,
あとこの朝ココ商品、まずこちらがね、あの私の叩くタイプのココパイ、おっぱいですね。
and for this Asacoco product, first, this is my striking type Cocopai, breasts, you know.
あのこちらストレスが溜まった時に、ぺーんって叩いてもらえば、あのストレスもなくなるのではないでしょうか！
If you pat it with a "thwack" when you're stressed, wouldn't your stress disappear too?
あとはこれココローション、あの、なんかの滑りをよくしたい時にね、
And then this Coco Lotion, when you want to make things slippery,
いくらでも使えますので、
you can use as much as you want,
わあうれしい！朝ココ商品がこんなに売れれば、
wow yay! If Asacoco products sell this much,
あの、じゃあねこちら、あの皆さんが買ってくれたこちらの商品、今からみなさんの脳内に、ぴん！発信いたします！
well then, this product that everyone bought, I will now transmit it directly to your brains, *ping*!
送信！送信！
Transmission! Transmission!
あ、今皆さんの脳内に送られましたね。
Ah, it was sent to everyone's brains just now.
あ、新たな注文を受け付けているようです。
It seems new orders are being accepted.
あ、ありがとうございます！こちらね、あの天使の耳、
Ah, thank you! Here, um, angel ears,
こちら1個1200万円になります。
these are 12 million yen each.
天使割引もされているから安心ですね！
Angel discounts are also applied, so you can rest easy!
ありがとうみなさん、たくさんのスーパークラッチそしてたくさんの応援いただいたおかげで、
Thank you everyone, thanks to all the super chats and the tons of support,
桐生ここは立派なヤクザになることができました！嬉しい！
Kiryu Coco was able to become a fine yakuza! I'm so happy!
あ、これこちらね、あの皆さん一番人気の商品になってますね。こちら、あの、ま決めるタイプの
Ah, this here, um, is everyone's most popular product. This, um, well, the deciding type...
言っちゃだめ？言っちゃだめすか？
shouldn't I say it? Shouldn't I say it?
ま、まあね、うん。今日3Dの配信がね、
Well, whatever, yeah. Today's 3D stream,
あのBANされるんじゃないかってスタッフの人がみんなね、ビクビクしているんですよ。
the staff are all being super jittery about whether it's gonna get banned.
あの、その証拠にね、私このようになく指を立てることを禁止されております。
As proof of that, I'm forbidden from raising my middle finger like this.
あの、あの指をVihallサンの時立てすぎたらね、あのこうやってね、あの動かなくされちゃうんで、みなさん気をつけてくださいね！
Um, if you raise that finger too much during Vihall streams, it stops moving like this, so everyone please be careful!
他の4期生も気をつけろ！スタッフは意外とYouTubeにビビってんぞ！
The other 4th gen members, watch out! The staff are surprisingly scared of YouTube!
このビビリ！この間にもたくさんの商品をいただいてみなさん、本当にありがとう！
Such cowards! Thank you so much everyone for getting so many products in the meantime!
あの、こちらですね、桐生ここの、あの、サスタイプ、はめるタイプの
Um, here, Kiryu Coco's, um, suspension type, fit-on type...
朝ココも、あのしっかりあるので、あ？
Asacoco also properly exists, so, huh?
なんすか？こっちにカメラが？どこにカメラなんだこっち？どこだこれどこ？あ、
What is it? The camera is over here? Where is the camera, over here? Where is this? Ah,
ここが可愛い、顔。
here is cute, face.
ねえ、みんなに見せられる場所ですか？
Is this a place where I can show everyone?
朝ココ商品を買うとこんなエゴーになれます！
If you buy Asacoco merchandise, you can get so smug!
でも、切なさの気持ちにもなる時があるでしょう？
But there are times when you might feel a bit melancholic, right?
みんな！でもこんなにたくさん愛してくれてありがとう！嬉しいよ！
Everyone! But thank you so much for loving me this much! I'm so happy!
そろさね、あの今回こちらを皆さんに改めて脳に直接発送いたします！まずっ！
So, um, this time we will deliver this directly to everyone's brains once again! First off!
ありがとうみんな！とても嬉しいよ！
Thank you everyone! I'm so happy!
たくさんみんなに愛されているって、とてもよく分かるよ。ありがとう！
I can really tell how much everyone loves me. Thank you!
そして、桐生会のピンが、ダイモンピンが発売されます！
And, the Kiryu-kai pin—Diamond pin is going on sale!
こちらスヤマもね、あの出たとこもんですけど、こちらになります
This Suayama too, um, as it appears, this is it,
桐生会ピンバッチ！所事情によりダイモンという文字を入れた場合怒られるのではないかということで、やはりベベタスタッフ、こちら桐生会のピンバッチということになっております、みんな！
the Kiryu-kai pin badge! Due to circumstances, if we included the word 'Diamond', we might get scolded, so after all, Bebetta staff, this is the Kiryu-kai pin badge, everyone!
これめっちゃ可愛いんで、やっぱ桐生会に入ってるならばね、これは必要なのじゃないですかね。
This is super cute, so if you're in the Kiryu-kai, isn't this necessary after all?
あれ、あれね、あの小指立ててるように見える？立ててないんですよ。
Huh? Huh, um, does it look like I'm holding up my pinky? I'm not holding it up.
やっぱYouTube君がセンシティブがセンシティブが苦手ってことですか？小指立てられなかったんですよ。
Does that mean YouTube-kun is bad with sensitivity? I couldn't hold up my pinky.
しかたがないね。スタッフがクソザコ言われてますよスタッフさん。
It can't be helped. Staff-san, you're being called weaklings.
まあ、消されるちゃうの怖いからね。
Well, because it's scary to get deleted.
まあ、私の桐生会はまだ始まったばかり、消される可能性も、カチコミを受ける可能性もまだまだありますからめちゃ怖い！
Well, my Kiryu-kai has just begun, and the possibility of getting deleted or raided is still there, so it's super scary!
皆さん、私の桐生会が生き残るために今ゲップ出ちゃった、失礼しました。あの桐生会が今後も生き残るためにどうかどうかよろしくお願いします！
Everyone, for my Kiryu-kai to survive—I just burped, excuse me. Um, for the Kiryu-kai to survive from now on, please, please I beg you!
あのたくさん動き回って、あのこれで、あの皆さんにたくさん私のね可愛い姿を見せることができたと思うのですけども、あの色々とと飛び回って飛び回ってぐるぐるして、あの
Um, moving around a lot, um, with this, um, I think I was able to show everyone my cute appearance a lot, but um, flying around and around and spinning, um,
楽しくこうやってやらせていただきましたが、だんだんと終わりのお時間は近づいているね。今日みんなあのちょっとお終いじゃの寂しいから、あの私にね、あの色々色々と、あっ
I had fun doing this, but the ending time is getting closer, right? Today, everyone, since ending is a bit lonely, um, give me, um, various things, ah
あっ、あの今情報が入りました！皆さん、ただいま情報が入りました！ブースで商品ページが公開されたようです！今すぐ見て！
Ah, um, information just came in! Everyone, information just came in! It seems the product page has been published in the booth! Go look right now!
でも買えないらしいまだ。でもその画面をセットしておいて、
But it seems you can't buy it yet. But set that screen up,
22時になったら見に行けばいいんじゃない
if it becomes 22:00, you can just go check it out,
あ、ちょ、しつこい、バカヤロー！机に入ってんじゃないのよ。
Ah, wait, stop being annoying, you idiot! It's not that I'm inside the desk.
なので22時になったら皆さん商品ページに行って、
So when it becomes 22:00, everyone go to the product page,
よかったら桐生会バッジを手に入れてください！お願いします！
and please get the Kiryu-kai badge! I beg you!
それではちょっと場所移動するぞ！れー！
Well then, I'll move locations a bit! Let's go!
おい！おい！おい！おい！おい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
同じ未来を見ていたい
We took our hands towards the brightest screens
あの夢手にしたい
All we wish are shinin' dreams
それぞれ違った
We make our choice with different voice
Oh yes we know Get set and GO!
You were the one who set this light of smile
it was a dark and hopeless place
It was your shiny eyes that caught me
Filled with hope, THIS STORY STARTS NOW
Notice the fear inside me bouncing up?
That's when I tune my heart beat down
I will shine, I will smile, my wish will come true
the first page of my history
Voice telling me to "Give it up"
Delete that word my heads are up
I will never be alone, no, not anymore
We are the shiny, smiley star!
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving all, we are now a team!
I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!
Let's show this world our dreamland!
Access through my heart, you will see
No regrets with hottest degree
We make our choice with different voice
Oh yes we know Get set and GO!
Glow to the top of my sky above
My precious shiny, smiley days
It's a light you have never seen before
Sending for you, C'mon and get it!
Do you remember all the love that you gave?
It's all here with me, I saved
Every voice, every word I get from you...
But not enough, I want it more
Your precious smile is like a spell
A magic dust that makes me smile
You'll never see my tears We defeat despairs
'cause it's my shiny, smiley life!
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
wonder story, ready to scream?
Together we can make it free
A never ending story
Everyone's a star in this tale
Filled with love and shine and a smile
We made our choice with different voice
Oh yes we know Get set and burst!
When I'm sad, you'll be here
When you're torn, I'll be there
Touch my screen and you will feel my heart here
Whenever you're near, there would be no fear
This beat will dry out every tears
Look at my future, shine and glow make every world to know
My shiny smile!
We took our hands towards our brightest stage
This is me, in my shiny page
Tear of joy and gold happy days
Just a start that we had just made
Hold my hands to see our "MIRAI"
Please my dreams come true for my life
Let the legend start step by step a miracle
We took our hands towards our brightest dreams
Giving our all, we are now a team!
I'll blow your mind! Now take my hand!
Let's show this world our dreamland!
Access through my heart, you will see
No regrets my heart is now free
We made our choices with different voices
Oh yes, we will create our WORLD
あのー、どうでした、皆さん、あの、頑張ったんですけど
Um, how was it, everyone? Um, I did my best, but
やっぱ、あの、先輩、レジェンドの先輩方が、あの、
you know, the seniors, the legendary seniors,
その、立ったステージに立つのは、恥ずかしすぎて、それぐらいだったらこの危険な、かき込みされた事務所の方が、マシかもって思って戻ってきちゃいました。
standing on that stage was so embarrassing, I thought coming back to this dangerous, scribbled-up office might be better.
失敗しちゃったし、恥ずかしいですよ。
I messed up, it's so embarrassing.
でも、あの歌詞、私が全部英語にして、あの、頑張って考えて歌ってみました。
But, you know, I translated all the lyrics into English, and I worked hard to think about it and sing it.
どうでしたか？
How was it?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あのね、あの英語の歌詞、実は私、あのデビューする前から考えていたもので、
You know, that English song's lyrics... Actually, I've been thinking about it before my debut,
あの皆さんの前で、いつか歌おうと思っていたんですけど、
and I was hoping to sing it in front of all of you one day,
やっぱりいつかならこの時しかない！
but I figured, if ever, there's no time like the present!
ない！ない！と思って、あの今やることにいたしました。
No! Now! So I decided to do it right now.
皆さん楽しんでくれていたら、本当に嬉しいです。
I'd be so happy if you all enjoyed it.
泣かないでよ、みんな！泣かないでよ！
Don't cry, everyone! Don't cry!
ありがとう、最高だった！
Thank you, it was the best!
全部自分で作ったんだ！
I made it all by myself!
気持ちを込めて、先輩方への敬意を込めて、作らせてもらいました。本当にみんな聞いてくれて、ありがとう！
I put my feelings into it, and my respect for my seniors, and they let me make it. Thank you so much, everyone, for listening!
あー。
Ah...
でもやっぱり、アイドル、こうやってステージで歌うの、すごい気持ちよかった。またステージに
But you know, being an idol and singing on stage like this felt amazing. To return to the stage...
戻る、行ってきまーす！うらあっ！
I'm heading back! Urah!
これが、これがステージ。
This is... this is the stage.
お客さんもいっぱいるよ、怖いよ。
There are so many customers too, it's scary.
でも、でもやっぱり私はこのライブの、桐生ココ。このライブに入ったのは、
But... but still, Kiryu Coco, of this live... Joining this live...
アイドルになるため。世界中のみんなが、
was to become an idol, so that everyone around the world
夢があると思ってもらえるような、アイドルになるために、
could feel like they have dreams, to become an idol,
そしてこのステージに立つために、先輩が立ってめちゃくちゃアイドルをしていたこのステージに立つために来たんだ！
and to stand on this stage... I came to stand on this stage where my seniors stood and were total idols!
だから、やっぱり、私は、私は、これからも、アイドルでいたいっていう思いが、今とっても芽生えていまーす！
So, after all, I... I still have this feeling that I want to continue being an idol, and it's sprouting up so much right now!
あの、とってもこの歌も練習したんだよ、みんな！
You know, I practiced this song so much too, everyone!
失敗しちゃったけど、失敗しちゃいますけども。
I messed up, though. I messed up, but...
あの、本番で、やっぱ難しい、歌って難しいよ。でも先輩が言っていた、あの絶対に練習は裏切らないからって。
You know, in the actual show... singing is hard. But my senior said, "Practice will never betray you."
だからこれからも、練習頑張るから！私頑張るからー！
So I'm going to keep working hard on my practice! I'll do my best!
また頑張りますから！あの、また次歌うときは、もっといいものにできる
I'll do my best again! You know, next time I sing, I'll make sure it's even better,
ようにしますね。あの、あの
okay? You know...
ちょっと最後に、あのガチ恋、ガチ恋してほしいから。やっぱアイドルとしてちょっとやっぱ、
You know, lastly... I want you to have a crush on me, a real crush. After all, as an idol, just a bit...
あのアイドル桐生ココってことをみんなに知ってもらうためにちょっと、かわいらしく、最後はかわいらしく、これがアイドル。どう？
to let everyone know that I'm Kiryu Coco the idol, a bit cute... lastly, cute... this is an idol. How's that?
スクショタイム、スクショタイムだよ。もう終わりの時間が近づいてるからね。
Screenshot time, it's screenshot time. The ending time is getting close, you know.
恥ずかしって！あの、みんな、あのガチ恋距離じゃないよ！ガチ恋距離だよ！誰だよ、ガチ恋距離って言ってるやつ、コメントこら！
So embarrassing! You guys... I'm not at real crush distance! It is real crush distance! Who's saying "real crush distance"? Check the comments!
コメントに、コメントにヤクザがいるよ。みんな、本当に本当に今日は来てくれて、本当にありがとう！
There's a yakuza in the comments. Everyone, thank you so much for coming today!
もうそろそろね、このステージ、この生配信も終わりになってしまいます。
We're almost reaching the end of this stage and this live stream.
桐生ココ今日3Dになりました！みんなのおかげで、あの、アイドルって素晴らしいって思ってます！
Kiryu Coco became 3D today! Thanks to everyone, I think that being an idol is wonderful!
やっぱり事務所も危ないし、やっぱヤクザってすごいなんか危険な、危険だし、4代目会長だけど私
After all, the office is dangerous, and yakuza are really dangerous, and even though I'm the 4th chairman, me...
アイドルに、アイドルに戻るわ。戻るっていうか、アイドルなんだけど、あ、アイドルヤクザよりも、アイドルになる！
Returning to being an idol. Or rather, I'm an idol, but... ah, becoming an idol, even more than an idol yakuza!
アイドル桐生ココ、これから頑張りまーす！
Kiryu Coco the idol, I'll do my best from now on!
みんな、私はアイドル！もうどこからどう見てもアイドルの桐生ココであるために！
Everyone, I'm an idol! So that no matter how and where you look, I am Kiryu Coco the idol!
ヤクザ、卒業します！アイドルとしてこれからは生きていきます！清純を目指す！清純アイドル、このライブ大
I'm graduating from the yakuza! From now on, I'll live as an idol! Aiming for purity! Pure idol, this live—
え？後ろ？後ろ？え？何何何何！
Eh? Behind? Behind? Eh? What what what what!
おらあ！
Raaah!
チンペラー！
Punk!
桐生会総力でぶっ潰してある！
The Kiryu-kai is going to crush you with all its might!
メルクスとホロライブシュリケン！
Secret Hololives Shuriken!
手裏剣！
Shuriken!
へいみんな、天音かなたです。
Hey everyone, it's Amane Kanata!
ここの3Dすごかったねみんな！
Coco's 3D was so amazing, everyone!
ちょっと感動してしまいましたが、
I was so moved by it, though...
えー、ちょっとみんな、実は僕も
Um, everyone, actually, I also...
7月1日(水)夜の配信で
on July 1st, Wednesday night's stream,
すっごい大切なお知らせをするから、
I'll be making a super important announcement!
絶対に絶対に観に来てください。
So please, definitely come see it!
本当、みんなみんな本当に観に来て、本当お願いします。ね、お待たせしてます、みんな来てね！
Really, I'm waiting for you all, so please come!